Tree Fruit Research Center, Wenatchee Records 1924-1973
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Correspondence
  - V-Z, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 363)
  - with various depts. of Wash. state, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 364)
  - with Wash. State Hort. Assoc., 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 365)
  - with Whirlpool corporation, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 366)
  - with WSU President French, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 367)
  - re. purchasng office (Box 8, Folder 368)
  - to staff and personnel office, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 369)
  - memo to Keene, Philip (Architect office), 1962 (Box 8, Folder 370)
  - with Controller's office, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 371)
  - with Controller's office (voucher approval), 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 372)
  - with retirement and insurance-Controller's office James Anderson, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 373)
  - with Graduate School-Dean D. S. Farner, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 374)
  - re. utility and accident reports, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 375)
  - with Agric. Exp. Stations, Lowell Rasmussen, assistant director, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 376)
  - re. buildings and grounds, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 377)
  - with Agric. Exp. Stations, Mason Milter, Editor, Assist. to Director George A. Bowman, Asst. Editor, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 378)
  - with Institute of Agric. Sciences, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 379)
  - with Agric. Exp. Stations, (Leonard Youg, Ass't. to Director, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 380)
  - with Agric. College, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 381)
  - with Agric. Exp. Stations, Mark Buchanan, Director, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 382)
  - with Agric. Exp. Stations, Walter Zuger, Financial Officer, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 383)
  - with Western Wash. Exp. Station, Puyallup, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 384)
  - with Dept. of Agric. Chemistry, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 385)
  - with Dept. of Agronomy, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 386)
  - with Dept. of Agric. Engineering, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 387)
  - with Irrigation Exp. Station, Prosser, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 388)
  - with Southwestern Exp. Station, Vancouver, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 389)
  - with Western Wash. Exp. Station, Mt. Vernon, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 390)
  - with Controller's Office, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 391)
  - with Dept. of Entomology, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 392)
  - with Dept. of Horticulture, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 393)
  - with WSU Hort. Extension Service, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 394)
  - with US Public Health, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 395)
  - with Dept. of Plant Pathology, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 396)
  - with misc. WSU depts., 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 397)
  - with WSU Controller's office, 1964-1971 (Box 8, Folder 398)
  - with General Stores, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 399)
  - re. pear rootstocks, 1965-1969 (Box 8, Folder 400)
  - Correspondence of finance officer (Zuger and Forbes), 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 401)
  - Correspondence of Ass't. to Director, Leonard Young, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 402)
  - re. motor pool, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 403)
  - Carl Pettibone's correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 404)
  - with WSU Payroll Office, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 405)
  - with WSU President and Vice President, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 406)
  - Correspondence of Ass't. Director Harold Singleton, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 407)
  - Correspondence with Louis L. Madsen (Dean of College of Agric. WSU), 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 408)
  - with Agric. Extension Service, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 409)
  - with Department of Agronomy, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 410)
  - Hobby's correspondence, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 410)
  - Jim Eakin's correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 411)
  - Chennault correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 412)
  - Chmelir (Senior Exp. Aide)'s correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 413)
  - with the Purchasing Office of WSU, 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 414)
  - with Ext. Station's editor, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 415)
  - Kirkpatrick's correspondence with Abdul Hamild of Dept. of Plant Pathology, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 416)
  - Kirkpatrick's correspondence, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 417)
  - with Wash. State Hort. Assoc., 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 418)
  - with Manson Irrigation Advisory Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 419)
  - Benson correspondence A-W, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 420)
  - Benson correspondence C-L, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 421)
  - Benson correspondence S-W, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 422)
  - Benson correspondence M-R, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 423)
  - Correspondence with Dept. of Water Resources, (Fiedler), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 424)
  - re. apple quarantine (Japan), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 425)
  - Correspondence A-W, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 426-440)
  - Correspondence A-R, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 441-452)
  - Correspondence, R-Z, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 453-456)
  - Correspondence A-Z, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 457-474)
  - Correspondence, 1968
    - -Anthon, Ted (Box 10, Folder 475)
    - -Benson, Nels (Box 10, Folder 476)
    - -Burts, Everett (Box 10, Folder 477)
    - -Covey, Ron (Box 10, Folder 478)
    - -Hoyt, Stan (Box 10, Folder 479)
    - -Ketchie, Del (Box 10, Folder 480)
    - -Kirkpatrick, Hugh (Box 10, Folder 481)
    - -McRitchie, Jack (Box 10, Folder 482)
    - -Stevens, Amie (Box 10, Folder 483)
    - -Sabbatical leave (Stan Hoyt) (Box 10, Folder 484)
  - Correspondence, 1969
    - -Anthon (Box 10, Folder 485)
    - -Benson, Nels (Box 10, Folder 486)
    - -Burts, Everett (Box 10, Folder 487)
    - -Covey, Ron (Box 10, Folder 488)
    - -Hoyt, Stan (Box 10, Folder 489)
  - Correspondence, 1970
    - -Ketchie, Del (Box 10, Folder 490)
    - -Stenvens, Arnie (Box 10, Folder 491)
  - Correspondence, 1971
    - -Anthon, Ted (Box 10, Folder 492)
    - -Benson, Nels (Box 10, Folder 493)
    - -Burts, Everett (Box 10, Folder 494)
    - -Covey, Ron (Box 11, Folder 495)
    - -Hoyt, Stan (Box 11, Folder 497)
    - -Ketchie, Del (Box 11, Folder 498)
    - -Misc. (Box 11, Folder 499)
    - -Stevens, Arnie (Box 11, Folder 500)
  - Correspondence, 1972
    - -Anthon (Box 11, Folder 501)
    - -Benson (Box 11, Folder 502)
    - -Burts (Box 11, Folder 503)
    - -Chmelir (Box 11, Folder 504)
    - -Covey (Box 11, Folder 505)
    - -Chennault (Box 11, Folder 506)
    - -Hoyt (Box 11, Folder 507)
    - -Ketchie (Box 11, Folder 508)
    - -Misc. (Box 11, Folder 509)
    - -Stevens (Box 11, Folder 510)
  - Correspondence and Memos A-R, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 511-525)
  - Memos Nordquist, D. J., 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 526)
  - Memos Oldenstadt, Dr. Dennis, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 527)
  - Memos re. Quarantine Permit, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 528)
  - Memos re. Washington Plant Quarantines, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 529)
  - Memos Shaw, Gardner, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 530)
  - Memos Shelton, V. L.-Finance, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 531)
  - Memos Smith A. H. (re. Sabbatical leave), 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 532)
  - Correspondence S-T, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 533)
  - Correspondence President Terrell, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 534)
  - Correspondence Tukey R. B., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 535)
  - Correspondence U, W, Z, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 536)
  - Larson Correspondence, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 537-560)
    - -Benson (Box 11, Folder 502)
    - -Burts (Box 11, Folder 503)
    - -Chmelir (Box 11, Folder 504)
    - -Covey (Box 11, Folder 505)
    - -Chennault (Box 11, Folder 506)
    - -Hoyt (Box 11, Folder 507)
    - -Ketchie (Box 11, Folder 508)
    - -Misc. (Box 11, Folder 509)
    - -Stevens (Box 11, Folder 510)
  - Correspondence and Memos A-R, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 511-525)
  - Memos Nordquist, D. J., 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 526)